Endpoint Security - Data Backup 
-----------------------------------------------------------
This safe folder is created by the Data Backup feature of Endpoint Security.
Data Backup automatically and periodically (multiple times a day), takes a backup of all your important and common files including PDF and Microsoft Office files in a safe folder on your computer. If you update any file, the feature will automatically take the backup of the latest copy.

For more information, contact Endpoint Security Administrator.

